mother has a sister and this
у матушки есть родная сестра и вот эта
sister sort of deceived mother and made it so
сестра как бы обманула маму и сделала
that mother took out a loan for herself
так что как бы Мама взяла кредит на себя
and this sister bought herself a fur coat for this
а эта сестра купила себе шубу за эти
money
деньги
that's cool And how much is this, how much is this
вот прикольно А сколько это сколько это
loan 200,000 there in the region of
кредит 200.000 там в районе
200 I mean what for  200,000 is Wait It
200 В смысле что за 200.000 это Подожди
turns out
Получается
140 so once again I'm
140 так ещё раз я что-то я в доллары
trying to convert something into dollars we divide by 100 200,000 and
пробую перевести делим на 100 200.000 а
2,000 dollars is a fur coat yes yes
2.000 долларов шуба дадада
yes yes Hello I'm absolutely glad to have you
дада Здравствуйте я ва категорически рад
let's have a normal conversation Look I'm
при давай нормально пообщаемся Смотри Я
originally from Rostov but I live in the USA in
сам родом из Ростова но я живу в США в
California 18  in about twenty years Booth
Калифорнии 18 лет через д двадцатка Бут
And where are you from
А ты откуда
I'm from Tomsk in Russia now a
сам я с Томска с России сейчас
contract soldier or a
контрактник или
volunteer at 19 years old I volunteered
к доброволец в 19 лет Пошёл добровольцем
Well a contract soldier for a contract
Ну контрактник на контракт
Well, actually Well, well I signed a
Да ну фактически Да ну те Подписал
contract yes, like that is, it turns out I
контракт да типа то есть получается
understood it's interesting And you it turns out it's like
понял интересно А ты получается это как
with the army  went Well, that is, to  conscript
с армией пошёл Ну то есть на срочник
got in and volunteered No, I
попал и пошёл добровольцем Да нет я
served my term Well, like 18 years old I went on
срочку отошёл Ну типа 18 лет Пошёл на
conscription, conscription, I served my term, I was discharged,
срочку срочки отошёл вышел на дембель
two weeks passed, I signed a contract and
недельки две прошло я Подписал контракт
left Cool And why
уехал Прикольно А зачем
Well, what kind of money
Ну какие денежные
or not, not money Well, in fact,
или нет не денежные Ну ну фактически
they give money, that's also it, but in general, no  Like, are you
деньги дают это тоже но в целом нет Типа
hiding from someone, there's a problem with the law
Прячешься от кого-то там с законом
or not?
пробле или не
Why would you
Зачем те бы
just announce it? Look, I don't understand what
оглашать просто Смотри я не понял какого
kind of problem you have, or do you want to fight or do
характера или тебе хочется воевать или у
you have some kind of problem there in civilian life
тебя какая-то проблема там на гражданке
that you needed a slab
что те нужно было сляб
or with the police?
или с полицией
No, I just can't.  understand well maybe I've
Нет я просто не могу понять ну я может
gotten out of the habit of this Russian Yes vibe I've
отвык от этого российского Да вайба я
been living in America for 18 years after all I can't
уже 18 лет живу всё-таки в Америке Я не
imagine what I needed for me
представляю что мне нужно было чтобы мне
now at 19 years old to take and throw everything and
сейчас в 19 лет взять и кинуть всё и
just go fight and die in a foreign
пойти просто воевать умереть в чужой
country Let's put it more simply so that you  we
стране Давайте скажем проще чтобы вы ни
didn't think about anything, don't
о чём не задумывались не
get hung up on it I love my Motherland,
зациклить Я люблю Родину свою вот так
let's do it this way, it will be simpler so there
давайте так будет проще чтобы вопросов
are no unnecessary questions, so how does your love for the
лишних не было так и в чём твоя любовь к
Motherland
Родине
manifest itself, I'm holding on
проявляется удерживаю
look at her uh I'm like Just me
её смотри ээ я как Просто у меня вот у
you only have parents Of course yes
тебя родители лишь есть Само собой да
look my mom and dad are in Rostov Yes
смотри у меня мама и папа в Ростове Да
they worked all their lives mom worked as a
они всю жизнь работали мама работала
nurse in the Rostov hospital now she
медсестрой в Ростовской больнице сейчас
gets a pension of 18,000 rubles the question is how is
получает пенсию 18.000 руб вопрос как
our richest Russia where there is oil
наша богатейшая Россия где есть нефть
gold  gas diamonds people get a
золото газ алмазы люди получает куниче
kuniche pension I have no idea honestly I have no
скую пенсию Без понятия честно без
idea I am not this not a diplomat not
понятия Я же не этот не дипломат не
some kind of Where does this money go Who do
какой-то там Куда деваются эти деньги
you think
Как ты думаешь кто их всех
takes it all I can't know that
забирает не могу знать то есть
is Putin and the gang take all
получается Путин и компашка забирают все
all the resources Yes they take everything  money My
все ресурсы Да забирают все деньги Моя
mom your mom your in Tomsk Yes mine in
мама твоя мама твоя в Томске Да моя в
Rostov yes lives on
Ростове да живёт на
beggarly and they send her to die in a
нищенское ещё и отправляют умереть в
foreign country
чужую страну
what's the joke how do you know that it
в чём прикол вы откуда знаете что это
is Putin who takes it It is his
вот именно Путин забирает Именно его
company who takes it and who is who Well he
компашка забирает а кто кто Ну он всё
controls everything he controls it
контролирует он же контролирует он
controls Russia And who Well, he doesn't have a
управляет Россией А кто Ну у него же не
billion hands to control everything in the
миллиард рук чтобы всё контролировать на
world again Well, look at how the flows of
свете ещё раз Ну смотрите как потоки от
gold, oil, gas and diamonds are
золота нефти газа и алмазов куда
dressed I don't know honestly I don't know I do
одеваются Я не знаю честно я не знаю Я
n't  I understand this Well, look at two
не разбираюсь в этом Ну смотри тут две
things here either Putin knows who is taking it
вещи либо Путин в курсе кто это забирает
and then he is an accomplice to this crime,
и тогда он соучастник этого преступления
or Putin is so stupid that he does not
да либо Путин настолько глупый что не
see how these billions are going somewhere,
видит как Эти миллиарды куда-то уходят
which means he is simply
значит он просто
the stupidest of all stupid, but not Probably
глупейшие всего глупый но не Наверное
I have little probability of that fact  that he
мне мало вероятность того факта что он
is the president Why does he need so much money
же президент Зачем ему так много денег
for what if he can see Bashar al-
для чего если он может их смотри Башар
Assad Yes, that one who fled to Russia,
Асад Да вот этот который убежал в Россию
he has a palace, a lot of money
так само у него дворец куча денег
Gaddafi was like the president, the head of the SI
Каддафи был типа президент глава си
Dictator also a lot of money Saddam Hussein
Диктатор тоже куча денег Садам Хусейн
Why do they all need money, yes  Do I know something
Зачем им всем бы денег да я что знаю что
or something It just works out Look Well,
ли Просто получается смотри Ну хорошо
if it doesn't work out that Putin He doesn't
если он не получается что Путин Он не
steal this money He's just so
ворует эти деньги Он просто настолько
stupid that he doesn't see how others steal
глупый что не видит как другие воруют
Well, probably I don't know I got it now
так Ну наверно Я не знаю понял теперь
look if such a stupid person doesn't
посмотри если такой глупый человек да не
see How they steal yeah  then maybe he
видит Как воруют да то может он и в сво
doesn't understand his own stuff maybe he started his own stuff for some reason
не разбирается может он зачем-то начал
and there's no need to start
сво а не нужно начинать
oh ha you want to talk about this Well,
ойха вы хотите про это поговорить Ну я
look, you're a military man I'm interested,
смотри ты же военный мне интересно вот у
I just have a classmate Sanya  Prokhorov
меня просто Одноклассник Саня Прохоров
is yes was more precisely we sat at the
есть да был точнее мы с ним сидели за
same desk in Rostov while Lenka was still not kif
одной партой в Ростове ещё Ленку не киф
there they threw papers I think he
там бумажками кидали по-моему вот
was a buddy yes we
дружбан был да мы до одиннадцатого
sat with him until the eleventh grade he went in the same year
класса с ним сидели пошёл тоже в
twenty-second he listened to this
двадцать втором году наслушался это
Solovyov Skobeev went to defend the motherland
Соловьёва скобеева пошёл родину защищать
Yes Solovyov  Yes Listen he's real here he is to
Да Соловьёв Да Слушай он реально вот он
me I called him on WhatsApp he
мне Я с ним по Ватсапу созванивался он
says not everything there NATO wants flight
говорит не всё там НАТО хочет лётное
time Banderites Nazis I say what you
время бандеровцы нацисты Я говорю ты что
look at You seem to have
посмотри Ты же вроде с красным дипломом
graduated from school with honors yes he
он закончил школу был да пошёл
volunteered in short they taught him something there
добровольцем короче что-то его там
everything  died, a drone flew right into his
научили всё помер прилетел Дрон прямо в
face, the Ukrainians also chased
лицо прилетел украинцы ещё это гоняли
this video, he's like running, running, the drone
это видео он типа бежит бежит Дрон его
catches up with him, in short, he loops,
догоняет он короче от него петляет
loops, loops, in short, Then he
петляет петляет короче Потом
stops, turns around, and the drone is
останавливается разворачивается и Дрон
right in his face and his head flies off, the
Ему прямо в лицо и башка отлетает
Ukrainians chased this video, in short, it was like
украинцы гоняли короче это видео типа
spinning his head, in short,  it was called like
крутило типа башку типа называлось типа
here's mom his mom like  sends
вот и мама мама его типа присылает
because his colleagues like showed how
потому что сослуживцы типа показали как
he died like sends I'm dun Damn it's brutal
он умер типа присылает Я ду Блин жесть
mom cries says like why is he
мама плачет говорит типа за что он
like yeah I've seen it a million times it's not scary
типа да это миллион раз видел не страшно
like I've already gotten used to it I'm not scared yeah
как бы я уже привык я суть не страшно да
Sanya Prokhorov won't be scared anymore either
Сане Прохорова тоже уже страшно не будет
He died yeah  The question is what did he
Он умер да Вопрос в том за что он
die for Well, it was his choice He wanted to go, he
погиб Ну это его был выбор Захотел пошёл
didn't want to go Yes, yes, well, why does it
не Захотел не пошёл да да ну зачем
turn out that Instead of being
получается Он вместо того чтобы быть
useful for his children, for his mother, for his
полезным для своих детей для мамы для
wife, like he's already Glory to him, may the earth rest
жены типа уже он Слава что земля ему
in peace, well, you turn out that's why you
пухом нун ты получается вот зачем вы
go and die in Ukraine Well because that's the
идёте гибни в Украину Ну потому что мы в
joke that's why we
том-то и прикол поэтому мы туда и
went there I don't argue I argue
пошли тут я не спорю я спорю
for money I love money very much And how much do
за деньгами деньги люблю очень А сколько
they pay now
платят сейчас
270,000 a month Yes And one-
270.000 в месяц Да А
time one-time 4 41 well 41 hardly like
разово разово 4 41 ну 41 врядли типа
they paid it now  tried or did you just
платили это сейчас пробовали или ты прям
go for 4 I got paid 300 at the moment
пошёл на 4 попал Мне выплатили на данный
when did you sign the
300 когда ты получается подписывал
contract it I signed it six months ago
контракт это Я подписал полгода назад 29
May 29 Well, six months ago was it really  4 million
мая Да ну полгода назад разве было 4 млн
payments then there was another 2 million, I think Well,
выплаты тогда ещё 2 млн было вроде Ну
it depends on which part you just
это смотря с какой частью просто
sign and that's it And where is it that
подписываешь и всё А где там такое что
four million in different parts, different
четыре ляма в разных частях разное
amounts of money are given to you, so to speak, for
количество денег тебе дают так скажем за
signing a contract I just watched the news,
подписку контракта я просто новости
like there because I'm a monitor
смотрел типа там потому что я монитор то
I'm interested I have some more
мне интересно у меня ещё некоторые
Odnoklassniki yes like I also
Одноклассники есть да то типа я тоже
saw that 2 million T is being offered now
видел что 2 млн Т вот сейчас предлагают
but there wasn't four
но четыре не было же
before Yeah And where do you want to put this money
раньше Ага А куда ты хочешь эти деньги
Yes I'll find where it's not a problem and
деть Да найду куда это не проблема а у
you have a wife children no no good  that
тебя есть жена дети не нету хорошо то
is, it turns out If you, like Sanya
есть получается Если тебе как Сане
Prokhorov, get in trouble This is in your face, yes, then
прохорову прилетит Вот это в лицо да то
who will receive compensation for you,
кто за тебя получит
mother, mother And what will mother
компенсацию матушка матушка А что мама
buy with this money? Well, that's her
купит на эти деньги ци Ну это уже её
business, what she wants Let them buy Well, what do
дело что хочет то Пускай покупают Ну как
you think Here What If mother
ты думаешь Вот Что Вот если бы маме
needed money or a son what would she
нужны были деньги или сын что бы она
choose
выбрала
Well she would continue to build her plot of land the
Ну она бы продолжила бы свой Участок
house would be arranged normally
отстраивать дом бы обустроила нормально
Well it is arranged normally it is just necessary as if
Ну нормально устроено просто надо как бы
this is in short her minor construction
это короче мелкие свои строительные
moments for example she would pay off the loan
моменты например она бы погасила кредит
Maybe I dont know I have no idea whatever she
Возможно не знаю я без понятия всё что
wants  and do what what kind of loan does
захочет то и сделать а что что за кредит
she have
у неё
Okay Okay let me tell you my mother
Ладно Хорошо давай те расскажу у матушки
has a sister and this sister And
есть родная сестра и вот эта сестра А
how would she deceive my mother and do it so
как бы обманула маму и сделала так что
that Mom would take out a loan for herself and this
как бы Мама взяла кредит на себя а эта
sister would buy herself a fur coat for this money
сестра купила себе шубу за эти деньги
that's cool  And how much is that, how much is that
вот прикольно А сколько это сколько это
loan 200,000 there in the region of
кредит 200.000 там в районе
200 I mean, what is 200,000 for Wait It
200 В смысле что за 200.000 это Подожди
turns out uh Well, the fur coat cost
Получается ээ Ну шуба стоил
140 so once again I'm
140 так ещё раз я что-то я в доллары
trying to convert it into dollars we divide by 100 200,000 and
пробую перевести делим на 100 200.000 а
2,000 dollars is a fur coat yes yes yes yes Yes Well,
2.000 долларов шуба дадада дада да А ну
like  maybe yes Okay, but you
типа может быть да А хорошо а вот ты
got the money, you didn't give it to your mom so
получил деньги ты мамке не закинул чтобы
she could
она кредит
close the loan Well, no, she doesn't know that I'm
закрыла Ну нет она не знает что я
here, I thought it would be better not to tell her Let it be
здесь я подумал что лучше не стоит ей
where And where does she think you are
Пускай во где А где она думает что ты
if she doesn't see you, all this  days Well I
если она тебя не видит все эти дни Ну я
call her I just call her on the phone
звоню я ей просто так по трубочке звоню
without a video call and all she thinks  that you are
без видеозвонка и всё она думает что ты
in Tomsk Yes, but I don't live in Tomsk, I
в Томске Да но я не в Томске живу я
was born
родился только
there in another
там в другом
city, it turns out that your mother doesn't
городе получается то есть твоя мама не
know that you've been at war for six months
знает что ты полгода на
Well, in fact, Yes, if you
войне Ну фактически Да если всё
think about it correctly, then that's how it is, it's
правильно рассудить то так и есть
cool, interesting, well, okay, but haven't you
прикольно интересно ну хорошо а ты не
tried it, for example  say that you are there You
пробовал например сказать что ты там Ты
earned there you are in the oil industry somewhere And
заработал там ты на нефтянке где-то И
so on on the shift you earned
так дальше на вахте ты заработал
send you money to pay off the
прислать тебе деньги чтобы погасить
loan no I haven't tried honestly
кредит не не пробовал честно
no Well look You got 4 million Yes for
нет Ну смотри Ты же получил 4 млн Да за
signing the contract of which 200,000
подписание контракта из них 200.000
can be taken to cover so that mom  In short, I didn't
можно взять покрыть чтобы мама Короче не
suffer with that loan, I wasn't worried. Well,
мучилась тем кредитом не переживала Ну
now there's more money here, they're
сейчас тут денег больше они у меня
just sitting in my account and everything is
просто на на счету лежат и всё там
much more there, but that's not the point. What's the point?
гораздо больше но не суть важно В чём
Why can't you? I can't
суть Почему ты не можешь Я не могу
understand why you can't throw some money at your mom now,
понять почему ты маме сейчас не можешь
like, so that  closed the loan
типа закинуть типа чтобы закрыла кредит
oh Honestly I didn't even think about it Well we
ой Честно я даже не думал об этом Ну мы
just I'm not arguing with you Yes
просто я ж не спорю с тобой Да я вот
I'm just a Russian who now lives in
просто я русский который живу сейчас в
California Yes you're a Russian who like
Калифорнии Да ты русский который типа
went to die in Ukraine Yes we
поехал типа умереть в Украину Да у нас у
each have our own choice I'm just  I don't
каждого свой выбор Я просто вот не
quarrel  you I'm interested in
ссорюсь тобой Мне интересно
the language as my
мова как сечас думают мои
compatriots think now That is, it turns out that
соотечественники То есть получается так
you won't throw money to your mom to close the loan And
ты мамке не закинешь закрыть кредит А
when you, like Sanya Prokhor, arrive, then your
когда тебе как Сане прохору прилетит то
mom will close the loan and finish building the site, it
мамка закроет кредит и участок достроит
turns out right now I'm right now
получается прямо сейчас я вот сейчас вот
after this after the call I'll throw some money just
после этого после звонка Я е скину денег
in case  firefighter She will simply
на всякий пожарный Просто она будет
ask where I got the money from and I
спрашивать А откуда у меня деньги а я
will say that I worked there on shift
скажу что что я там работал на вахте
say I worked on shift
скажи поработал на вахте
maybe that's the same you know today
возможно туж такое понимаешь сегодня
there is an opportunity to send money and tomorrow
есть возможность скинуть деньги а завтра
it's gone Well yes, that's just the thing that
уже нету Ну да просто в том-то су что
she is such a person that  she will pry everything out
она такой человек что она будет всё
until the end until she figures it out
долова будет до конца пока не разберётся
Where did this money
Откуда же эти деньги
come from, such a
взялись такой
person, you know, If
человек такое с понимаешь Если
for war Yes, this Olga Nikiforova
на войну Да вот у этой Ольги никифоровой
and what about you, the Light disappeared, and it
и и что у тебя Свет пропал а и
turns out that no matter how he
получается получается что как бы он
received the money, he did not send it to her
получал деньги ей не скидывал ему
a shell flew at him and she still
прилетел снаряд и она до сих пор не
can't get the money that was
может получить деньги которые были у
on his card you know well
него на карте понимаешь
I'm not a banker I don't know about something  svya not
ну я не банкир Я не знаю с чем-то свя не
Why Because look in order to
Почему Потому что смотри для того чтобы
get money you need to get it as
получить деньги нужно получить это как
it is inheritance to get inheritance
оно наследство чтобы получить наследство
Yes, yes, in order to get inheritance it is necessary that
Дада чтобы получить наследство нужно
6 months have passed after death Yes,
чтобы прошло 6 месяцев после смерти Да
in order to enter into inheritance And in order for there to be a
чтобы вступить в наследство А чтобы был
fact of death you need You need a body so that
Факт смерти нужно Вы нужно тело чтобы
there is no body He is listed  missing Yes,
нету тела Он числится пропавшим безвести
this Atams flew in there, like, or something
Да там прилетел этот атамс типа или что
Yes, just like everyone else who was there with him
Да его тупо как и всех кто там с ним был
Yes, and they found someone's remains, they
да Во и кого-то нашли останки там
identify someone there, no And so he's
идентифицируют кого-то нет И вот до сих
still not there, he's already gone, oh, he
пор нету его уже ай
fell away Well, that's a cool, cool conversation
отпал Ну это классный классный разговор
was for him like subscribe comment and
был за него лайк подписка коммент и
send to all friends This is just brutal
скиньте всем знакомым Это просто жесть
Yes, here they are 19 years for money because they
Да вот они 19 лет за деньги потому что
live in poverty and everything subscribe to my
живёт в нищете и всё подпишись на мий
Telegram right now axis VN and
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
keeps us busy through Scar George in yours  ban and
заня нас через Скар Георг в твый бан и
very many videos are not shown to people
дуже багато видео не показуе людям
sometimes show information about streams
вчасно показуе информация про стрими
That's why  so that we Mali operational
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
links are written right now and while there in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okm video there is also interesting and
телегра окм видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we will oblige you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
to keep the current operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с